Hanks, Paul; Papers apap253
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1944-1966; Undated; 1; 8.6 cubic ft.
  - New York State Vacationlands: Worlds Fair Edition, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - New York State's Land Farmers, Agriculture Business, Cornell, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - New York Women and Their Changing World, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - New Yorker's Health, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - News from the Speaker, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - News Letter, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - News Letter: Water Authority, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - News Map of World Outlook, Undated (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - News Paper Clippings Mentioning Hanks, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - News Paper Clippings Mentioning Hanks, 1964; Undated (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Notes, 1961; Undated (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Off-Track Betting, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Office for Local Government Newsletter, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Office of the Executive, Closing of Belmont Park Race Track, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Official Canvass of Monroe County, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Ohio River Valley Water Sanitation Commission, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Ohio River Valley Water Sanitation Commission Fifteenth Annual Report, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Olympics, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - On: Target, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Open Invitations, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Operation Advance- Fact Sheet Kit, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Opportunity Home, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Part II Federal Subsidies- an Unguided Force, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Pattern for New York? A Report on Off-Track Betting in England, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Paul Hanks' Assembly Memo, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Per Capita State AID: Issues Before the 1964 Legislature (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Personal, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Perspective on 1963 Economic Highlights of the year, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Pocket Guide to GOP Accomplishments at the 1965 Legislative session (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - "Police Protection More or Less", Undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Power Authority of the State of New York Annual Report, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Prayer Room in the United States Capitol, Undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Preliminary Fifteenth Annual Report of the Conservation Department for the Year 1960 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Preliminary Fifty-Third Annual Report of the Conservation Department, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Premium Bonds, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Preservation of the Verrazano Narrows Bridge Name, 1964 January 18 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Private Institutions in the Public Service: Report No. 39, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Proceedings of the Second Annual Governors Conference on Aging, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Program for New York State-Local Relationships, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Proposed 23rd Amendment to the Constitution, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Proposed Constitutional Amendments, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Public Housing, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Public Welfare, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Raccoon, 1963; Undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Rail Road Tugboat Strike, Undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Re-Apportionment, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Recommendation of the Law Revision Commission to the Legislature, Undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Recommendation to the 1961 Legislature: State of New York, 1961 February 6 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Reducing Cost of Public Education in New York State, Undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Regents Major Legislative Proposals for 1964 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Regents Proposals for the Expansion and Improvement of Education in New York State, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Regents Scholarship, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Regents Scholarship Letters, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Regents Scholarship Winners, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Regents Scholarship Winners, 1964; Undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Regents Winners, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Regulation of Public Utilities in New York State, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Remarks by the Honorable Joseph H. Murphy at the Legislative Seminar, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Remarks of Republican Candidate Joseph Demarrias, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Report: Relation to Civil Practice Law and Rules, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Report on Equal Representation for Equal Numbers of People, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Report of the Interstate Staff Committee, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Report of the Law Revision Commission for 1955, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Report of the Law Revision Commission, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Report of the New York State Joint Legislative Committee, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Report of the New York State Joint Legislative Committee on Migrant Labor, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Report of the Special Committee, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Report of Special Committee on Public Bar Relations, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Report to the New York State Legislature, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Report to the New York State Legislature, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Reports about Banks (1 of 2), 1959; 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Reports about Banks (2 of 2), 1959; 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Republican Committeeman, Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Republican County Committee Monroe County: New Release, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Republican Platform 1964, "For the People" (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Requests, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Requests-Closed, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Requests-Open, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Research Library, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Retired Teachers, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Roads: New York Good Roads Association, 1964 February (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Rochester Eye Bank and Research Society, Inc., 1963 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Rochester Gas and Electric, 1961; Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Safety Belts for Cars, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Sale of New York State Flags and National Flags, 1694 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Salaries for Faculty of State University, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Sample Question for Civil Service Examinations, Undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Savings and Loans Ass'n Mergers, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Saving Bank Association of New York State, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - SCAD, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Scholarship Incentive (1 of 3), 1964; Undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Scholarship Incentive (2 of 3), 1964; Undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Scholarship Incentive (3 of 3), 1964; Undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Scholarship Incentive for High school Students, 1964; Undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - School Aid, 1960-1961; Undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - School District Information, 1962; 1964 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Science Center, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Second Annual Report New York State Bingo Control Commission, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Second Report of the Temporary State Commission on Per Capita Aid, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Second Report of the New York State Temporary Highway Finance Planning Commission, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Social Welfare, 1963; Undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - SPEC Session 1, 1961; Undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - SPEC Session 2, 1961; Undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Speech Draft/Memo, 1964; Undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - State Advisory Council on Employment and Unemployment Insurance Report, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - State AID to New York City, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Sate AID to Schools 1963-64 Compared with 1958-59, Undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - State Budget 1961-1962, Undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - State Budget Process (Preliminary Draft Version), 1964 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - State Department of Public Works of New York, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - State Design of Highways and Cost, Undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - State Government News, November 1960, 1960 December (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - State Income Tax, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - State Income Tax Rebate, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - State Liquor Control, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - State Lottery Control Commission Second Annual Report, 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - State of New York Annual Budget Message, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - State of New York Conservation Department Two Year Progress Reports, 1961-1963 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - State of New York Department of Law, Undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - State of New York Executive Chamber Albany, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - State of New York Joint Legislative Committee on School Financing, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - State of New York Public Service Commission, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - State University of New York: The Master Plan, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - State University of New York (Master Plan), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Statement Before the Joint Legislative Committee to Revise the Banking Law, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Statement by Regents re Legislation Affecting Assignment of Pupils to School, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Statement of Legislative Principals, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Statement and Resolution of the Protestant Church, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Steps Toward better Education, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Suggested State Legislation Program for 1961 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Summaries of Rockefeller Other Studies, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Superintendent of Schools Newsletter, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Supplemental Budget for general Fund Purposes, Undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Supplemental Pension for Teachers, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Supplementary Report on Uniform Commercial Code, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Supreme Court Appellate Division, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Symposium on Use and Effects of Pesticides, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Tax Bulletin, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Tax Payer Information, Undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Taxable Status Day for Filing Veterans' Exemptions (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Taxation: Associated Industries of New York State Inc. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Teachers-5% Take Home Pay (1 of 5), 1961; 1963-1964; Undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Teachers-5% Take Home Pay (2 of 5), 1961; 1963-1964; Undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Teachers-5% Take Home Pay (3 of 5), 1961; 1963-1964; Undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Teachers-5% Take Home Pay (4 of 5), 1961; 1963-1964; Undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Teachers-5% Take Home Pay (5 of 5), 1961; 1963-1964; Undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Teachers Guide: Visiting the State Museum, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Teachers Union of the City of New York Memorandum on Governor's "Scholar Incentive" Plan, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Telegrams, Undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Telegrams from 1964 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - The 1961 Legislature, Undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - The Albany Report, 1961 February 2 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - The Association of the Bar of the City of New York, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - The Commissioner's Committee on Reference and Research Library Resources, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - The Conservative Party of New York State, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - The Council of State Governments, Undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - The Dilution of Higher Education: Report No. 38, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - The Fallacies and Dangers in the Proposals to Abolish the Federal Income Tax, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - The Ford Foundation Annual Report, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - The Government of New York State, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - The Grange Speaks in 82nd Annual Session, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - The John Burroughs Memorial Association, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - The Legislature of the State of New York Members, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - The Metropolitan Milk Producers' News (February), 1964 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - The National: Gambling Inc., 1960 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - The New York State and Local Tax System, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - The New York Sate Council of Churches, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - The New York State Joint Legislative Committee on Problems of the Aging, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - The New York State Tax Payer, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - The New York Wight Distance Tax, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - The Official Law Paper for the First and Second Judicial Departments, Undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - The Opportunity and Rehabilitation Center Program, 1960 December (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - "The Peoples Stick", Undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - The Public Schools of New York City Staff Bulletin, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - The Record in the Field of Rural Areas, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - The Republican Committeeman and the Campaign, Undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - The Rockefeller Republican Record, undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - The Savings Bank Depositor, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - The Second Sphinx (The True Story of the "World Trade Center"), Undated (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - The State Legislative Programed of the Liberty Party for 1964 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - The Uniformed Sanitationmen's Association, Undated (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - The University of the State of New York the State Education Department, 1961 February 1 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - These are your Congressmen, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Those Who Vote, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Time Off to Vote, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Times Union, Picketing Humanity, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - To the Legislature About Bills Relating to Liquor, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - "To the Members of the New York State Senate and Assembly", 1960; Undated (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Tours at the New York State Capital, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Town Highway Improvement Program Twelfth Year, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Traffic Safety Needs, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Transit Study Committee, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Trucking, 1964; Undated (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Truth for Youth New York, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Tuition, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Tuition, Undated (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - T.V. Technicians License Bill, 1961; Undated (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Ulster Commentary, 1961 January (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Unemployment Compensation, Undated (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Use of Cars at State University at Brockport, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Village Committee, 1961; 1963-1964; Undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Visiting School Groups to the State Museum, 1964; Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Voice of New York Business, 1960-1961; 1964 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Ways and Means Committee Agenda, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Ways and Means Committee Resolutions, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Ways and Means Committee-Welfare (1 of 2), 1961-1964; Undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Ways and Means Committee-Welfare (2 of 2), 1961-1964; Undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Ways and Means Correspondence, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Ways and Means-Labor, 1961; 1963-1964; Undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - WCBS-TV Editorial Broadcast, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - WCBS Editorial, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Weekly Legislative Summary, 1961; 1964 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Weekly News Letters, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Welfare Residency Law, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Western Expressway, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - What You Should Know About New York Waters, Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - "When You Gamble you Risk More Than Your Money", Undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Why Motor Vehicle Inspection, Undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - "Why Separate Contracts for Public Works in the State of New York", 1964; Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Wins Radio Rent Control Must Stay, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Winter Tours J.L.C., 1961; 1963 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - W.R.C. Home at Oxford, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - YMCA Secretaries to Youth and Government, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Your- Health… Happiness… Prosperity, Undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Your Out Door Recreation Map, Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Legislation, 1961-1965; Undated; 2; 1.3 cubic ft.
  Series 2 contains legislation introduced by Hanks as well as support from his constituents. It also includes background information on the laws being introduced and Hanks' evidence on why they should be adopted.
  - 1964 Legislation Recommendations of New York State Agriculture Businessmen Council (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ABC Laws (1 of 2), 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ABC Laws (2 of 2), 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Acts Introduced by the Committee on Rules, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Amend the Act to Enable Counties to Impose Tax on Admission to Horse Race Meets, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - An Act Establishing an Economic Conversion Commission, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - An Act to Amend the Alcoholic Beverage Control Law, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Service Law (1 of 2), Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Service Law (2 of 2), Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - An Act to Amend the Public Authorities Law, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Assembly Seats and Legislation Bills, 1961; 1963-1964 (Flat-file 1)
  - Bills to be Considered, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Conservative Party Legislative Rating Service, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Data in Support of the Mayor's Legislative Fiscal Program, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Deficiency Appropriation, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Empire State Highway Transportation Association, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - General Fund-State Purposes Fund, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Hardship Bill A.I. 3220-S.I. 2089 Nowicki-Dominick, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - I. 62, P. 62, An Act to Amend the Banking Law, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - I. 119, P. 119, An Act to Amend the Military Law, Undated; 1963 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - I. 120, P. 120, An Act to Amend the Military Law, Undated; 1963 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - I. 121, P. 121, 1943, An Act to Amend the Education Law, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - I. 122, P. 122, An Act to Amend the Labor Law, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - I. 513, P. 513, An Act to Amend the Retirement and Social Security Law, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - I. 1054, P. 1054, An Act to Amend the Workmen's Compensation Law, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - I. 1151, P. 1151 An Act to Amend Military Law, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - I. 1458, P. 1458, An Act to Amend the Code of Criminal Procedure, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - I. 1560, P. 1560, An Act to Amend the Education Law, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - I. 1674, P. 1676, An Act to Amend the Retirement and Social Security Law, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - I. 1834, P. 1834, An Act Making Deficiency Appropriations for the Support of Government, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - I. 1953, P. 1959, 2607, An Act to Amend the Conservation Law, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - I. 1954, P. 1960, An Act to Amend the State Finance Law and Civil Service Law, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - I. 1990, P. 1998, An Act to Amend the Education Law, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - I. 2006, P. 2011, 5732, An Act to Amend the Justice Court Act, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - I. 2146, P. 2151, An Act to Amend the Education Law, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - I. 2274, P. 2292, An Act to Amend the Labor Law, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - I. 2400, P. 2431, An Act to Amend the Education Law, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - I. 2412, P. 2443, An Act to Authorize the Gates-Chili-Ogden Sewer District of the County of Monroe, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - I. 2444, P. 2475, An Act to Amend the Social Welfare Law, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - I. 2460, P. 2491, An Act to Amend the Optional County Government Law, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - I. 2461, P.2492, An Act to Amend the Optional County Government Law, 1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - I. 2462, P. 2483, An Act to Amend the Correction Law, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - I. 2514, P. 2544, 5478, An Act to Amend the Education Law, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - I. 2535, P. 2566, An Act to Amend the Workmen's Compensation Law, 1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - I. 2688, P. 2729, An Act to Amend the Conservation Law, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - I. 2689, P. 2730, An Act to Amend the Conservation Law, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - I. 2690, P. 2731, 5479, 5937, An Act to Amend the Election Law, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - I. 2691, P. 2732, An Act to Amend the Election Law, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - I. 2692, P. 2733, An Act to Repeal Article Twenty-One of the Tax Law, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - I. 2693, P. 2734, An Act to Repeal Article Twenty-One of the Tax Law, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - I. 2694, P. 2735, An Act to Amend the Civil Service Law, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - I. 2695, P. 2736, An Act to Amend the Retirement and Social Security Law, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - I. 2780, P. 2867, An Act to Authorize the Council of Rochester to Sell Land, 1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - I. 2796, P. 2972, An Act to Amend the Membership Corporations law, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - I. 2811, P. 2835, 4993, An Act to Amend the Labor Law, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - I. 2829, P. 2938, An Act to Amend Insurance Law, 1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - I. 2830, P. 2939, An Act to Amend the Insurance Law, 1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - I. 2940, P. 2964, An Act to Repeal Sections Fifty-Four, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - I. 3025, P. 3134, An Act to Authorize and Empower the Adjutant General, 1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - I. 3040, P. 3097, 4999, An Act to Amend the Banking Law, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - I. 3055, P. 3130, An Act to Amend the Abandoned Property Law, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - I. 3056, P. 3131, An Act in Relation to Certain Commercial Transactions, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - I. 3228, P. 3288, An Act to Amend the banking Law, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - I. 3041, P. 3150, An Act to Amend the Correction Law, 1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - I. 3042, P. 3151, An Act to Amend the Optional County Government Law, 1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - I. 3229, P. 3289, An Act to Amend the Banking Law, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - I. 3316, P. 3386, An Act to Amend the Public Health Law, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - I. 3317, P. 3387, 5320, An Act to Amend the Labor Law, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - I. 3341, P. 3411, An Act to Amend the Election Law, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - I. 3389, P. 3459, An Act to Amend the Chapter Three Hundred Sixty of Laws Nineteen Hundred Eleven, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - I. 3403, P. 4282, An Act to Amend the Public Authorities Law, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - I. 3408, P. 3538, An Act to Amend the Banking Law, 1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - I. 3409, P. 3539, An Act to Amend the Banking Law, 1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - I. 3411, P. 3541, An Act to Amend Civil Service Law, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - I. 3431, P. 3501, 5829, An Act to Amend Uniform Commercial Code, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - I. 3530, P. 3600, 5830, An Act to Amend Uniform Commercial Code, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - I. 3531, P. 3601, 5856, An Act to Amend Uniform Commercial Code, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - I. 3675, P. 3830, An Act to Agriculture and Markets Law, 1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - I. 3676, P. 3831, An Act to Amend the Conversation Law, 1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - I. 3703, P. 3804, An Act to Amend the Village Law, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - I. 3704, P. 3804, An Act to Amend the Court of Claims Act, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - I. 3705, P. 3806, An Act to Amend the Court of Claims Act, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - I. 3706, P. 3807, An Act to Amend the Court of Claims Act, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - I. 3707, P. 3808, An Act to Amend the Court of Claims Act, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - I. 3783, P. 3942, An Act to Amend the Workmen's Compensation Law, 1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 85)